Nurul Uhkrowi

Contact

- uhkrowi@gmail.com
- t.me/uhkrowi
- github.com/uhkrowi
- linkedin.com/in/uhkrowi

About

Having experience in coding since 2016, I've been working on both small and large projects. I have a lot of experience in full-stack web development. Usually write in Go, (and formerly in PHP, C# and NodeJS). Love to learn any new interesting technologies.

Project

BIMA: Lecturers Research
Management System (2023)
Indonesian Lecturers' Research
Management System.

Graha Multimedia Nusantara:
Company Profile (2022)
Company Profile Website of Graha
Multimedia Nusantara.

Omni Channel Management System (2021)

Enables businesses to provide a seamless and integrated customer experience across multiple channels.

Experience

 Front-End Web Developer • Full-time • Remote
 PT. Elektronik Distribusi Otomatisasi Terkemuka (eDOT)

06/2022 - 07/2023

Building back-office of eLOG's platform for managing partner, customer and all distribution and delivery purpose.

Stacks: React.js • Next.js • Tailwind CSS • Web Development

• Full-stack Web Developer • Freelance • Remote PT. Idea Nusantara Cipta

04/2022 - present

As A Freelance Web Developer. Building a research management application system of lecturers of Indonesia.

Stacks: Go • React.js • Docker • Cloud Run (GCP) • Google Cloud Storage

Back-end Web Developer • Body Hire • Remote
 PT. Astra International Tbk

12/2021 - 05/2022

As a body hire from PT BeIT, joined into Astra team to modify their existing system and focusing on tax regulation.

Stacks: .NET • C# • SQL Server

• Front-end Web Developer • Freelance • Remote PT. Perjalanan Menembus Galaksi

08/2022 - 11/2022

Worked on designing, building web components and integrating with APIs of an online shop back-office.

Rental Housing Management (2021)

Managing the supply and demand of rental flats, private and public housing.

Meeting Room Management (2020)

A mobile application serves as a comprehensive meeting management tool.

Skill

HTML • CSS • Go • JavaScript •
React.js • Next.js • MySQL •
PostgreSQL • WordPress • Git •
GCP • Micro Services • Rest API •
Web Development

Education

Politeknik LP3I Jakarta Information Technology 2016 Stacks: JavaScript • Vue.js • Nuxt.js • Tailwind CSS

• Front-end Web Developer • Full-time • Remote

PT. BelT Inovasi Tiwikrama

01/2020 - 05/2022

Creating prototypes based on mockups, integrating with web services of enterprise Data Center Management system and do back-end stuffs when necessary.

Stacks: JavaScript • Vue.js • Tailwind CSS

• Back-end Web Developer • Full-time • Remote

PT. Idea Nusantara Cipta

11/2017 - 10/2019

Built an enterprise system for a learning institution in Indonesia. Some of the services are Academic, E-Learning, Human Resource and Finance.

Stacks: .NET • C# • PostgreSQL • Microsoft Azure

• Full-stack Web Developer • Full-time • Remote

PT. IndoVisual Presentatama

02/2016 - 11/2017

Developing smart home and office from scratch, integrating hardware to control and automate them with system.

Stacks: Node.js • Java • Python • MySQL • SQLite • Angular.js